<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>4.2.4</latestVersion>
    <url>https://github.com/steve1316/uma-android-automation/releases</url>
    <releaseNotes>
v4.2.4 - Changelog

New
---
- Add new buttons to the MessageLog component to sort ascending or descending.
- Add new buttons to the MessageLog component to scroll to the top/bottom of the log.
- Add a preview screen to review what settings will be overwritten when importing a settings JSON file.
- Add a new option to the Misc section of the Settings page to display message log IDs.
- Add a new Profile function to the Training Settings page to allow for creation/management of profiles to switch between. Import/Export logic has also been updated to handle Profiles as well. Example: Keeping separate customized profiles for Mile and Long runners.
- Add a new option to the Training Settings page to allow the user to set a custom stat cap to stop training on other than the default of 1200.
- Add a new option to the Training Settings page to allow the user to train Wit during the Final instead of recovering energy.
- Add a new option in the Misc section of the Settings page to stop the bot before the Finals on turn 72
- Add POST_NOTIFICATIONS permission to the AndroidManifest.xml file to potentially help people who are not encountering the popup to enable notification permission.
- The package.json file now has 2 new commands for quicker testing of the app.
- Add Android logic to perform one-time scenario validation check to ensure that the bot is running the correct scenario (Unity Cup for now).
- Add a note to the Racing Plan Settings page to remind users to check their selected races after making changes to the filters.

Adjustments
---
- Update game data up to Halloween Rice Shower and Super Creek.
- Bump version of Automation Library to incorporate some improvements to the message log handling.
- Adjust warning message regarding Debug tests in the Settings page to clarify that it is not required for the tests to run.
- Change some error messages to be shown as Snackbar notifications.
- Shift priority weight for event chains for TrainingEvent class to prioritize guaranteed recreation/dating for supports like Riko.
- Update date detection logic to better handle the Finals in-game dates.
- Update logic to dismiss the scheduled race popup warning when executing a training at the end of the Training process.
- Remove unnecessary fields from settings before exporting to cut down on the size of the exported JSON file.
- Change the Focus on Spark 

Fixed
---
- Fix most instances of log messages being out of order in the MessageLog component.
- Fix bug where mood recovery could not be completed if dating was available and already completed. Example: Riko Support.
- Fix rare bug where the intro message in the MessageLog component would be missing the app name and version due to missing dependency in the callback function.
- Fix bug where "Finale Underway" was not being parsed correctly by GameDateParser.
- Fix bug where risky training was not being started when the initial failure chance was not being checked with the risky training threshold.

    </releaseNotes>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>